Guide to the Poly Archives Portrait Collection RG.028
Poly Archives at Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology
- W
  - Wishnick, William, undated (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Witryk, Ted, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Witt, Christopher J., undated (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Witte, Arnold, undated (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Wojan, Clifford, undated (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Wolf, Barry, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Wolf, Edward L., undated (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Wolfe, Don M., undated (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Wolfgang, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Woll, William K., 1966 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Wong, Edward K. "Ted", undated (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Wonsicki, Edward A., Jr., 1959 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Wotherspoon, Neil, undated (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Wovomestko, Frederick, undated (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Wright, Chilton A., undated (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Wuestefeld, [Richard ?], undated (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - Wulff, [Raymond ?], undated (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Wulfken, Howard J., 1953, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - Wunsch, Joseph W., 1959, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Wunsch, Elsie and Martin, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Wunsch, Samuel, 1958, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 87)
- Y
  - Yang, Deane, undated (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Yang, Yisong, undated (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Yanis, Edward M., undated (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - Yates, Chauncey V., Jr., undated (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - Yates, Janet, undated (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - Yeoman, Neil, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Ying, Nelson, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 94)
  - Yokelson, Bernard J., undated (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Yokelson, Marshall V., undated (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - Yoon, Lisa, undated (Box 9, Folder 97)
  - Youla, Dante C., undated (Box 9, Folder 98)
  - Young, Morris, undated (Box 9, Folder 99)
  - Yousoufian, Hrant H., undated (Box 9, Folder 100)
  - Yuan, [J.], undated (Box 9, Folder 101)
  - Yusim, Galina, undated (Box 9, Folder 102)
- Z
  - Zabar, Zivan, circa 1995 (Box 9, Folder 103)
  - Zach, Theodore A., 1955 (Box 9, Folder 104)
  - Zahner, [Richard ?], undated (Box 9, Folder 105)
  - Zauderer, Erich, undated (Box 9, Folder 106)
  - Zeldin, Martin, undated (Box 9, Folder 107)
  - Zerban, Alexander H., undated (Box 9, Folder 108)
  - Zhang, GaoYong, undated (Box 9, Folder 109)
  - Ziegler, Edward, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 110)
  - Ziegler, Henry Martin, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 111)
  - Ziehl, Charles, undated (Box 9, Folder 112)
  - Zienkowicz, J.J., 1943 (Box 9, Folder 113)
  - Ziv, Nina, undated (Box 9, Folder 114)
  - Zito, Frederick A., undated (Box 9, Folder 115)
  - Zitzmann, Frank Richard, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 116)
  - Zlatanova, Jordana, undated (Box 9, Folder 117)
  - Zucker, Frederic E., circa 1980 (Box 9, Folder 118)
  - Zuckerman, Robert, undated (Box 9, Folder 119)
  - Zurawsky, Walter, undated (Box 9, Folder 120)
  - Zworykin, Vladimir K., undated (Box 9, Folder 121)
- Miscellaneous
  - Unknown- Polytechnic Fellows, undated (Box 9, Folder 122)
  - Unknown, undated (Box 9, Folder 123)
  - Unknown, undated (Box 9, Folder 124)
  - Unknown, undated (Box 9, Folder 125)